A Guide to the Peter F. Geithner papers FA1408
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professional and personal files, first run, 1963-2004; 1; 23.73 Cubic Feet About 57 LTR size Hollinger boxes, 1 Half-LTR size Hollinger box, and 4 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - Centre for Advancement of Philanthropy (CAP) - Diaspora Indians - on the Philanthropy Fast-Track, Priya Viswanath, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 656)
  - Make it Powerful – Tap Diaspora Philanthropy to Resource: An example for Taiwanese Americans, Snow Lee, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 657-658)
  - Faith based Giving from a Distant Land: Hindu Diaspora and Religious Philanthropy, Priya Anand, 2003 May (Box 49, Folder 659-660)
  - China University of Political Science and Law (FADA)/Temple University Business Law Center (BLC) Program on Environmental Law, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 661-663)
  - China University of Political Science and Law (FADA)/Temple University Masters of Law Program (LLM) and Business Law Center (BLC) - Program proposal, circa 1999 (Box 49, Folder 664-665)
  - China University of Political Science and Law (FADA)/Temple University Masters of Law Program (LLM) and Business Law Center (BLC) - Program proposal, 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 666-667)
  - Temple University law programs in China, 2000-2002 (Box 49, Folder 668)
  - China University of Political Science and Law (FADA)/Temple University of Law/American Bar Association (ABA) Business Law Section Program, 1997-2000 (Box 50, Folder 669-671)
  - United Nations Commission on Population and Development 36th Session - Keynote Address of Amartya Sen, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 672)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2001 (Box 50, Folder 673)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Greentree Foundation, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 674)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2001 (Box 50, Folder 675)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Human Security Now: Protecting and empowering people, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 676)
  - Fourth Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow: Human Security as a Policy Framework for New Cooperation in Asia, 2001-2002 (Box 50, Folder 677)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2000-2001 (Box 50, Folder 678)
  - Human Security in Crisis and Transition: A Background Document and Application, working draft by Jennifer Leaning and Sam Arie, 2000 September (Box 50, Folder 679)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 1999-2001 (Box 51, Folder 680-683)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 1999-2001 (Box 51, Folder 684-685)
  - Canadian Consortium on Asia Pacific Security (CANCAPS) Bulletin, 2000 November (Box 51, Folder 686)
  - Ford Foundation - Organization of Program Work (Sample Reference Materials), 1998 (Box 51, Folder 687)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2001 (Box 51, Folder 688)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - First Meeting, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 689)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - First Meeting, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 690-691)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 1998-2001 (Box 51, Folder 692-693)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 694)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Human Security Now: Protecting and empowering people, 2001-2003 (Box 52, Folder 695)
  - Asian Perspectives on Human Security: A Responsibility to Protect?, Paul Evans - Revised draft, 2003 July (Box 52, Folder 696)
  - Human security, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 697)
  - Ever New Horizons: The Story of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1922-1975, William P. Fenn, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 698)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) - Review Meeting notes and Ed Baker report, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 699)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Review, 1986-2003 (Box 52, Folder 700-702)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Review - 4 Bryant, Cambridge, Massachusetts House, 1997-2003 (Box 52, Folder 703)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Review, 1998-2003 (Box 52, Folder 704)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 705)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2002 (Box 52, Folder 706)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 1999-2002 (Box 53, Folder 707-710)
  - Ever New Horizons: The Story of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1922-1975, William P. Fenn, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 711)
  - Sailing on Winds of Change: Two Decades in the Life of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1969-1990, Paul T. Lauby, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 712)
  - University for a Night: Synergos at the United Nations, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 713)
  - Hawaii family visit, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 714)
  - Temple University Beasley School of Law Business and Comparative Law Center - Progress Report, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 715-717)
  - Tokyo, Japan trip, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 718)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Washington D.C. meeting, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 719)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Tokyo, Japan meeting, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 720)
  - Institute for International Policy Studies (IIPS): International Conference on The Role of Non-Profit Organizations in the Civil Society in the 21st Century, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 721)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) - China-Japan-U.S. trilateral relationship, 2000-2001 (Box 54, Folder 722)
  - Institute for International Policy Studies (IIPS) - International Conference on The Role of Non-Profit Organizations in the Civil Society of the 21st Century, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 723-724)
  - The Aspen Institute - Executive Seminar Asia, 2000-2001 (Box 55, Folder 725)
  - Montana vacation, 1990-2000 (Box 55, Folder 726)
  - Brochures regarding human security, undated (Box 55, Folder 727)
  - Third Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow: Cross-Sectoral Partnerships in Enhancing Human Security, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 728-729)
  - Third Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow: Cross-Sectoral Partnerships in Enhancing Human Security - Agenda, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 730)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 Second Annual Conference, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 731-732)
  - The Philippine American Chamber of Commerce, Inc. - The Honorable Manual A. Roxas III, Secretary of the Department of Trade and Industry, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 733)
  - Harvard University Asia Pacific Regional Governance Workshop series, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 734)
  - Hong Kong trip, 1999-2000 (Box 55, Folder 735)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Workshop, 1999-2000 (Box 55, Folder 736)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Workshop, 1998-2000 (Box 55, Folder 737)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Executive Committee Meeting, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 738)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Fourth Africa Program Meeting, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 739)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Fourth Africa Program Meeting, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 740)
  - Neelan Tiruchelvam Commemoration Programme, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 741)
  - New Delhi, India trip, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 742)
  - University of British Columbia Vancouver Liu Centre for the Study of Global Issues, 1998-2000 (Box 56, Folder 743)
  - University of British Columbia Vancouver Institute of Asian Research/University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2000 (Box 56, Folder 744)
  - University of British Columbia Vancouver Peter Wall Institute for Advanced Studies, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 745)
  - University of British Columbia Vancouver - Migration from China Workshop, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 746)
  - St. Barth's vacation, 2000-2001 (Box 56, Folder 747)
  - Envelope from U.S. Deputy Chief of Mission in India Galen L. Stone, circa 1968-1973; File contains a still image addressed to Peter F. Geithner and his wife Deborah from U.S. Deputy Chief of Mission Galen L. Stone. The individuals depicted within include Peter and Deborah Geithner as well as their four children, Timothy, Sarah, Jonathan, and David. The photograph was taken by R. N. Khanna in New Delhi, India. It is undated, but because the envelope in which it was sealed was addressed to the Geithners' address in New Delhi, it is likely that it was taken at some point during Peter F. Geithner's time as Ford Foundation Deputy Representative for India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka (1968-1973). (Box 56, Folder 748)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Review, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 749)
  - Temple University School of Law with China University of Political Science and Law (FADA) - Master of Laws Program, undated (Box 56, Folder 750)
  - Temple University law programs in China and Japan, 2003-2004 (Box 56, Folder 751-752)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Intellectual Exchange grant proposals, 2003-2004 (Box 57, Folder 753-756)
  - Asia Development Research Forum (ADRF): Shaping Asia's Voice – Challenges of Economic Integration and Challenges of Ageing, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 757-759)
  - Asia Development Research Forum (ADRF): Shaping Asia's Voice – Challenges of Economic Integration and Challenges of Ageing, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 760)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Field Staff Workshop, Nairobi, Kenya, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 761)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets regarding conflict management, business education, and economic issues in Asia, undated (Box 57, Folder 762)
  - Asia Development Research Forum (ADRF) - Asia Advisory Council (AAC), 2000-2001 (Box 57, Folder 763)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Field Staff Workshop, Nairobi, Kenya, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 764)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 Third Annual Conference: Managing Globalization - Summaries, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 765-766)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 Third Annual Conference: Managing Globalization, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 767)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 Third Annual Conference: Managing Globalization, 1999-2001 (Box 58, Folder 768)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Advisory Committee Meeting, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 769)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 Third Annual Conference: Managing Globalization, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 770)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 771)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation Science-Based Development Program: How We Invest in Human Capital, Joyce Lewinger Moock - with Geithner's notes, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 772)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Program Theme Guidelines, 1999 December (Box 58, Folder 773)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Regional Activities in a Global Foundation, 1999 October 28 (Box 58, Folder 774)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation Science-Based Development Program: How We Invest in Human Capital, Joyce Lewinger Moock, 1998 February 9 (Box 58, Folder 775)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Africa-Based Program Staff Responsibilities, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 776)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Biotechnology in food production, 1999 December (Box 58, Folder 777)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - History publication, policy, and proposed plans, 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 778)
  - FEMED Newsletter Special Issue: Minds Across Africa School Clubs, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 779)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Uganda Country Program, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 780)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1998-2000 (Box 58, Folder 781-782)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Regional Activities/Africa, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 783)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Representative for Southern Africa and Director for Africa, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 784-785)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Directory of Selected African Research Networks, 1998 April (Box 59, Folder 786)
  - Rockefeller Foundation 1999 Trustee Curricula Vitae compilation (Box 59, Folder 787)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees - Asia trip, 1994-2000 (Box 59, Folder 788)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Preliminary budget and budget statements, 1997-1999 (Box 59, Folder 789-790)
  - Letter from Patrick O'Heffernan, 1999 October 26 (Box 59, Folder 791)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Africa Program, 1997-1999 (Box 59, Folder 792)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - New program structure, 1997-1999 (Box 59, Folder 793-794)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Report of the Nairobi Regional Office Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 795)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Africa Program, 1999-2002 (Box 59, Folder 796)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - United Nations Security Council Watch, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 797)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Program Venture Experiment (ProVenEx), 2001 December 21 (Box 59, Folder 798)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Overview of Revised 1998 Budget and Initial 1999 Budget (Box 60, Folder 799)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - the Philanthropy Workshop (TPW), 2001 (Box 60, Folder 800)
  - Cove House Endeavors (CHE) - Orleans, Massachusetts, 1963-1998; File contains five still images (Folder 801). These images are photographs of a property. (Box 60, Folder 801-804)
    Restricted - financial material
  - International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX), 1998-2001 (Box 60, Folder 805)
  - International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX) Asia Advisory Committee, 1997-2001 (Box 60, Folder 806)
  - Nomura Mutual Funds, 1998-2001 (Box 60, Folder 807)
  - Overseas Development Council (ODC), 1995-2000 (Box 60, Folder 808)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Year 2000 Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 809-811)
  - Rockefeller Foundation consultancy appointment, 1997-1999 (Box 61, Folder 812-813)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Budget Working Group, 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 814)
  - Ford Foundation - Policies concerning expatriate staff, 1994-1999 (Box 61, Folder 815)
  - Rockefeller Foundation 1996-1997 Asian countries budgets, circa 1996-1997 (Box 61, Folder 816)
  - International Conference on Health Research for Development, undated (Box 61, Folder 817)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Introducing Learning and Liaison presentation, 1999 October 28 (Box 61, Folder 818)
  - Preferential Pricing Structures in Public/Private-Sector Collaborations: Report to the Rockefeller Foundation by Program for Appropriate Technology in Health (PATH), 1999 March (Box 61, Folder 819)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - African Population and Health Research Center (APHRC) review, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 820)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - the Philanthropy Workshop (TPW), circa 2000 (Box 61, Folder 821)
  - RF Flex and other benefit information for Rockefeller Foundation field staff, 1992-1998 (Box 61, Folder 822)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Proposed Program Budget System, 1997-2000 (Box 61, Folder 823-824)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Regional Activities in a Global Foundation presentation, 1999 November 9 (Box 61, Folder 825)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Budget Working Group, 1997-1999 (Box 62, Folder 826-828)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 829)
- Professional and personal files, second run, 1951-2011; 2; 18.02 Cubic Feet About 40 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 6 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  This series contains the segment of Peter F. Geithner's professional and personal files that was originally organized in boxes labeled 1-14D.
  Personal correspondence at the end of the series chiefly consists of letters and notes written to Geithner by his wife and children when he was abroad with the Ford Foundation in the mid-1970s.
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR), 1996-2002 (Box 63, Folder 830)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Financial Statements, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 831)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR), 2000-2002 (Box 63, Folder 832)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Executive Committee Meeting, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 833)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Annual Members' Meeting, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 834)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) - Ford Foundation survey of programs involving U.S.-China relations, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 835)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2001-2002 (Box 63, Folder 836)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 837-838)
  - Conference on U.S. Media Coverage of China, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 839)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Strategy Committee, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 840)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) 2001 Annual Report, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 841)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) - Supreme Court Justice Anthony Kennedy proposal, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 842)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Strategy Committee, 1998-2003 (Box 63, Folder 843-845)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 846)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Strategy Committee, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 847)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Executive Committee Meeting, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 848)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) 2002 Annual Report, 2003 August (Box 64, Folder 849)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Program Committee - Conference call, 2003 May 9 (Box 64, Folder 850)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 851)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Gala Dinners, 2001-2003 (Box 64, Folder 852)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR), 2003 (Box 64, Folder 853)
  - Soviet Union trip - Trans-Siberian Express, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 854-855)
  - Asia-Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC) Conference - Strengthening Philanthropy in the Asia Pacific: An Agenda for Action background papers, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 856-857)
  - Asia-Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC) Conference - Strengthening Philanthropy in the Asia Pacific: An Agenda for Action Summary Paper draft, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 858)
  - Asia-Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC) Conference - Strengthening Philanthropy in the Asia Pacific, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 859)
  - Asia-Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC) Conference - Strengthening Philanthropy in the Asia Pacific, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 860)
  - England and Ireland trip, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 861)
  - Ford Foundation Monograph Authors Meeting, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 862)
  - Workshop on Accountability and International Nongovernmental Organizations (INGOs), 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 863-864)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Tokyo, Japan meeting, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 865)
  - U.S. Council for Security Cooperation in the Asia-Pacific (USCSCAP) - Washington D.C. meeting, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 866)
  - China trip, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 867)
  - Beijing, China trip, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 868)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Fellow, Paige Evans, 1998-2000 (Box 65, Folder 869-870)
  - Genoa, Italy visit, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 871)
  - Italy vacation - Geithner's 70th birthday celebration, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 872)
  - World Economic Forum (WEF) - India Economic Summit, 2000-2003 (Box 65, Folder 873)
  - World Economic Forum (WEF) - India Economic Summit, 2002-2003 (Box 66, Folder 874)
  - Stanley Foundation - Strategy for Peace Conference (SPC), 2003-2004 (Box 66, Folder 875-876)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Tokyo, Japan meeting, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 877)
  - Fifth Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow - Tokyo Workshop, Summary of Discussions, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 878)
  - Fifth Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow - Tokyo Workshop, 2000-2003 (Box 66, Folder 879)
  - Tokyo, Japan trip, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 880)
  - Florida visit, 2002-2003; File contains a still image depicting three individuals believed to be Peter F. Geithner, his wife Deborah Moore Geithner, and his brother Paul Geithner. (Box 66, Folder 881)
  - Harold Howe II memorial, 1969-2003 (Box 66, Folder 882)
  - Fifth Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow - Bangkok Workshop, 2000-2002 (Box 66, Folder 883)
  - International Public Symposium: Challenges to Human Security in a Borderless World, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 884)
  - International Public Symposium: Challenges to Human Security in a Borderless World, 2002 (Box 66, Frame 885)
  - Report of the Commission on Human Security (CHS), draft, 2002 November (Box 66, Folder 886)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2001-2002 (Box 67, Folder 887)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Bangkok, Thailand meeting, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 888)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment, 1999-2003 (Box 67, Folder 889)
  - The Ford Foundation's International Cooperation Program in Vietnam: A Report to the Ford Foundation by Peter F. Geithner, 2002 July 18 (Box 67, Folder 890)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment, 2002-2003 (Box 67, Folder 891)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF) Asian Advisory Council and Steering Committee Meeting, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 892)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF) General Meeting, 2002-2003 (Box 67, Folder 893)
  - The Role of Philanthropy in Postwar U.S.-Japan Relations: Pocantico Workshop, 2002-2003 (Box 67, Folder 894-895)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 Fourth Annual Conference: Thinking Long Term, 2001-2002 (Box 67, Folder 896-897)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 898)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 Fourth Annual Conference: Thinking Long Term, 2001-2002 (Box 68, Folder 899)
  - Bangkok, Thailand trip, 2001-2002 (Box 68, Folder 900)
  - Dartmouth College Careers in Cross-Cultural Understanding panel, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 901)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI) - Global Philanthropy Writer's Workshop, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 902)
  - Swan's Island, Maine Memorial Day visit, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 903)
  - Siem Reap and Angkor, Cambodia visit, 2000-2002 (Box 68, Folder 904)
  - Geithner's 70th birthday, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 905-906)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS) - Stockholm, Sweden meeting, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 907)
  - Florida visit, 2001-2002 (Box 68, Folder 908)
  - Philanthropy for Global Equity meeting, Tokyo, Japan, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 909)
  - Fourth Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow: Human Security as a Policy Framework for New Cooperation in Asia, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 910)
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office 50th Anniversary, 1997-2002 (Box 68, Folder 911)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment - Expenses, 2001-2002 (Box 68, Folder 912-913)
  - Miscellaneous reports regarding Taiwan and Cross-Strait relations, 2000-2002 (Box 69, Folder 914)
  - National Committee on American Foreign Policy (NCAFP) Roundtable on U.S.-China Relations and the Taiwan Issue, 2001-2002 (Box 69, Folder 915)
  - U.S.-China Chamber of Commerce (USCCC), 1999 (Box 69, Folder 916)
  - U.S. China Chamber of Commerce (USCCC), 1997-1999 (Box 69, Folder 917)
  - International Institute for South Asian Affairs (INSAF) South Asia Forum, 1997-2003 (Box 69, Folder 918-919)
  - International Institute for South Asian Affairs (INSAF), 2003 (Box 69, Folder 920)
  - International Institute for South Asian Affairs (INSAF) Meeting at Uganda House, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 921)
  - International Institute for South Asian Affairs (INSAF) promotional material, undated (Box 69, Folder 922)
  - India Center of Art and Culture (ICAC), 1998-2002 (Box 69, Folder 923)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2002-2003 (Box 69, Folder 924)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 925-926)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 1999-2000 (Box 70, Folder 927-928)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 1999 (Box 70, Folder 929)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI) Occasional Paper No. 15 - Thirteen Years of Power Sector Reform in India: Are We Still Groping in the Dark?, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 930)